那见鬼的魔鬼训练还真有用
Hey. Fucking hecklers drill really worked.
有个女孩朝我脸扔瓶子  我以牙还牙了
This girl threw a bottle at my face, smashed it back at her.
你们刚在那里演绎了死亡之舞
You did the death dance in there.
让那些混球知道什么叫气势锐不可挡
You showed those punks how to cockfight.
你收了演唱会的钱了吗
Did you get the money for the concert?
-没  你们免费演出  -什么
- No, you played for free. - What?
这肮脏的行业  先投资才有回报
Takes money to make money in this filthy business.
-想在客厅里唱还是开演唱会  -演唱会
- Wanna play living rooms or stadiums? - Stadiums.
我可是用他们的电话搞定了你们去海外的巡演
I racked up their phone bill booking your tour overseas.
-海外  真的  -那当然  先冷静下来
- Overseas, really? - Yeah. Easy.
你们先在车里把钱交了
You gotta pay your dues first here on the road in a van,
然后飞机就来接你们
...then come the jets.
-我们什么时候出发  -我可不上路
- When do we leave? - I don't go on the road.
我会和你们的监护人谈的  散开跑啊
I'll talk to your keepers. Scatter!